seolinkslist.com 2013-04-30

# 

Privacy Policy seolinkslist.com/sapforums, respects the privacy, integrity and security of the visitors. We use sound security measure to protect your identity and information so that any third party could not use your personal information without your prior consent. We will not disclose, sell or rent any of your personal information to the third party however we cannot warranty the security of the information as no data is safe and protected on the internet. We collect information and data using cookie, however user can disable the cookie. The purpose of the cookie is to collect useful information about the user’s interest and provide useful advertisements, it also help us in improving the services. There are many advertisement links displayed on the seolinkslist.com/sapforums, but the website is not responsible for the third party link advertised on the website. Click these links on your own risk as seolinkslist is not responsible for the content, policies or practices of such third parties. These sites may collect personal information from you. It is advised to read privacy policy of these sites to avoid any problem. Some ads on the website are put by Google. These Google ad scene are managed by the Google. Google use DART cookies to store the user information and use this information to serve the user better by displaying relevant ads. The DART does not track personal identifiable information about user, but user may opt out of the use of the DART cookie. visiting the http://www.google.com/privacy/privacy-policy.html For the fast and assured listing and acceptance of your listing please follow our link submission policy. Thanks & Regards
